（ベル坊）スー…スー…。
（男鹿）おおっ！？
こ　これは…？
Look at this... It reverted?
戻った？
オ～ッ　戻った！戻った～！！
Yeah! It's reverted!
Reverted!
戻った戻った～戻ったよ～！！
Reverted, reverted! Reverted at last!
（ヒルダ）何を小踊りしている。
What are you prancing on about?
フフフ…見てのと～りよ！
Read it and weep.
ハッ…貴様！！せっかく増えた
ゼブルスペルを！！
You fool! You finally increased
the Zebul Spell, and...
((貴様がボロクソに
相手を殴れば殴るほど→
The power will grow the more you
beat the crap out of your opponents.
その力は強まり
真の魔王へ近付くという訳だ))
Coming ever closer to the
true power of a Demon Lord!
ハ～ッハッハッハッ！
ま～　なんつ～の？
Oh, yeah? What was that again?
オレって　やっぱ
善良な市民ってやつですから。
See, I'm just your average
upstanding citizen!
貴様…！！
おとなしくしてりゃ
ざっと　こんなもんよ！
You fiend...
As long as I stay well behaved, this
thing goes right back to the way it was!
おとなしく？
ああ。
Well-behaved?
１週間　家に引きこもって
ゲームしてたぜ！
I stayed cooped up at home for
a week playing video games!
（グシャッ！！）
この　クソニートが。
あ～っ！
You piece of shit slacker.
オレの１週間の結晶が～！！
Everything I gained over the past week, gone!
（アランドロン）
＜これは　ひょんな事から
赤ん坊を育てる事になった→
This is a story of a high school
juvenile delinquent who,
不良高校生の物語＞
through some strange circumstances,
is raising a baby.
＜ただし　その赤ん坊は
普通の赤ん坊ではなく→
But this baby is no ordinary baby.
魔王の子だったのです！＞
It is a baby Demon Lord!
Toys Have Arrived from the Demon World
Oh no you didn't!
てめえ　ふざけんなよ！！どんだけ
オレが大冒険したと思ってんだ！！
Do you have any idea how
grand an adventure I had?
オレの１週間の
スペクタクルを返せ～！！
Give me back my week of glorious splendor!
Stop whining.
わめくな…。そんな物より→
I've brought better toys than that.
もっといい　おもちゃを
持ってきてやった。
あ？おもちゃ！？
Huh? A toy?
坊っちゃまと一緒に遊べる
魔界の　おもちゃだ。
It is a toy from the Demon World which you
and the master can play with together.
取りに帰るのに
少々時間がかかったがな。
It took quite a while to go and pick it up.
そ～いや　いねぇと思ったら
魔界に帰ってたのかよ。
Ah, I was wondering where you disappeared
to. Went back to the Demon World?
ふむ…組み立てが必要らしいな。
It looks like it needs to be set up.
Hey, don't just stand there. Help.
おい　突っ立ってないで手伝え。
ああ？
坊っちゃまが寝ている間に作るぞ。
We'll finish it up while
the master is sleeping.
で　こりゃあ　何作ってんだ？
So, what exactly are we making here?
ふむ　説明書が　どうも不親切でな。
This instruction manual
isn't being very helpful.
簡易遊戯ルームのようなものだと
思うのだが…。
I thought it was a simple play room, but...
んっ　これは！？
ん？
This is...
（カチッ）
な　なんだ？
まずい！！
What the...
Oh, no!
うむ…完全に
閉じ込められたようだな。
It looks like we're completely trapped.
なに　しれっと言ってんだよ！！
ど～ゆ～ことか説明しろや！
How can you sound so calm?!
Explain what the hell's going on!
説明？貴様に説明したとして
何の意味がある？
Explain?
What would be the point of explaining
to a simpleton like you?
クーッ！！
オレに気を使えっつってんだ！
Throw me a bone here, damn it!
なんでだ？
「なんでだ」じゃね～だろ！
Why?
Why not, huh?!
スー…。
つまるところ　どうやらこれは→
Basically, this is similar to what in
the human world you call an insect cage.
人間界で言うところの
虫カゴのような物らしいな。
虫カゴ？
うむ。
Insect cage?
Yes.
（説明書）説明を始めるよ！→
Let's begin the instructions!
今日は家族でピクニック。→
Say that today we're having a family picnic!
And suddenly, a rare magical beast appears!
ところが　そこに
偶然　レア魔獣を発見！→
I want to capture it, but I don't
have any items handy on me!
でも　捕獲したいけど
手持ちのアイテムがな～い！→
な～んてこと　あるよね！
ね～よ！
Doesn't that just, like, always happen?
Uh, no.
For times like those...
そんな時は　これ…！→
It's the "Portable Magical Beast Capture
Cage!" No monster can get away!
どんな魔獣も逃しません！
「どこでも魔獣捕獲籠」だぁ？
Portable Magical Beast Capture Cage?
要するに　魔獣を捕まえる籠に
捕まっちまったってことか。
So we've been trapped in a cage
that's for holding magical beasts...
うむ。
で　ど～やったら出られんだ？
Yes.
Then how do we get out of here?
ん～まあ　待て。
Wait.
さらに箱の開け閉めには
お子様の遊び心を刺激する→
Furthermore, the opening
and closing of the cage,
is controlled by key blocks, a children's
toy that will stir their hearts!
キーブロック式を採用。
キーブロック？
あれだな。
Key blocks?
Those, I presume.
（説明書）型はめ遊びをしながら
籠の開け閉め。→
As they play with the blocks and
holes, the cage opens and closes.
これを解かないと
絶対に籠は開きません。
If you can't solve it, the
cage will not open, ever!
You can take that feature and shove it!
いらね～だろ　その設定！！
Not opening! Not opening!
I's ain't openin' no how!
（説明書）あきません　あきません
わて　ほんま　あきません。
つ～か　何なんだ　その説明書！
おちょくってんのか！！
And what the hell's with that manual?
It's makin' fun of me!
なお　組み立てる時は　必ず外から
組み立てて下さい（笑）。
Therefore, during assembly, make
sure to stand on the outside (LOL).
Keep the LOLs to yourself!
笑うな～！！
とにかく　ここは坊っちゃまに→
Anyway, we must get the
young master to unlock it.
あれを解いてもらうしかあるまい。
マジかよ…。
Are you kiddin' me?
坊っちゃま。
おい　ベル坊！
Master!
Hey, Baby Beel!
スー…。
おい　起きろ！！
坊っちゃま！
Wake up already!
Master!
スー…　ふみ？
起きた！
坊っちゃま！
He's awake!
Master!
ダブ…アイッ…。
アウ…アッ？ア～！
You idiot! Not that direction!
バカッ　こっちじゃね～よ！！
声が届いておらんな。
ベル坊！
Can he not hear us?
Baby Beel!
ダブ…？アッ？アイ！！
通じた！？
うむ　伝わったようだ！
He got it!
Yes! It seems he understands!
ダ！アイアイ！！ウ～！
Master!
坊っちゃま～！
何がして～んだ　てめ～は。
What the hell is he doing?
イー！
おお？
さすが　坊っちゃま！自力で
おもちゃの存在に気づいたようだ。
Yes Master, excellent! You've realized
there's a new toy all by yourself!
ダーブ！
All right! Now take that block and...
よ～し！あとは　そいつを！！
なんで　ベッドの下に！？
...put it under the bed?!
ダッ！
と見せかけ　はめに行った～！
But it was just a feint!
アイ？アイ！ダーッ！！
あいつの知能は
チンパンジー以下か？
Is he stupider than a chimpanzee?
ぼ　坊っちゃま！
おやめ下さいまし！
Master! Please stop that!
壊れてしまいます～。
You're going to break it!
（グシャッ）
（爆発音）
ダ～ッ！アイ～！！
マジかよ…。
Are you kiddin' me?
まさか　ずっとこのままなんて
言うんじゃね～だろ～な…。
Don't tell me I'm going to
be stuck in here forever...
《ん！？これは…》
This is...
ふざけんなよ…。
To hell with that.
ざけてんじゃ…ねえ！！
No way, no how...
ダーブー！！
ぶっこわ～すっ！！
I'll destroy this thing!
（爆発音）
ダーッ！！アーイ！！
《坊っちゃまと離れながらにして
魔力を引き出した…》
He pulled out magic power despite
being separated from the master...
フッ…。
ハッハハハ…！！
ど～だ　見たか～！
こなごなだぜ～！！
ダーブ！アイー！！
Hey, you see that?
I punched the thing to smithereens!
うむ。ゼブルスペルも
戻ったことだし。
And the Zebul Spell has
returned to its former state.
ああ？
めでたしめでたし。
Congratulations, it's a happy ending for all.
んなっ！！
アイ！アブ～！！
ダ～ブ～！！
喜んでんじゃね～よ！！
What're you so happy about?!
We Played Doctor
Principal
（古市）ふ～ん。それで
１週間の大冒険がね～。
So you had a grand adventure this past week?
（古市）っつっても　前よりは
減ってんじゃねぇか。
Well, it's less than it was before, anyway.
That's because I've been good
for three days since then.
またそれから３日間ぐらい
おとなしくしてたんだよ。
If you think you can defeat
me, then go ahead and try!
No matter what attack you use, I...
（グシャッ！）
((アイ…！))
((ギャーッ！！))
Hilda-san really doesn't hold back, does she?
（古市）容赦ね～な～　ヒルダさん。
That damn woman thinks violence is
the answer to life's problems...
あの女　何でも暴力で
解決しようとしやがって…。
お前が言うか。
You're one to talk.
Anyway, it's finally gone back this much.
とにかく　ようやく
ここまで戻ったんだ。
If I can just stay good
for another 2-3 days...
あと２～３日
おとなしくしてりゃ…。
今回は絶対に乗り切ってやる。
This time I'm definitely
gonna manage it somehow!
So therefore, in order to be an
upstanding citizen, you will assist me.
つ～わけで　善良な市民で
いるために協力しろ。
お前が外に出て　暴れなかった
試しがね～じゃね～か。
Has there ever been a case where you've
gone out and not caused an uproar?
I thought I told you to assist me!
協力しろっつってんだろ～が！
ググッ…！！
ほら　暴れてんじゃね～か！
See? You're going on a rampage!
ん？おいっ！
ああ？
Hey!
What's that?
あれ何だ？
ん？
ダブ！アイ～！！アイ！
Oh, those are toys from the
Demon World that I haven't used.
ああ　使わなかった
魔界のおもちゃだ。
I have to bring them with me to
prevent Baby Beel from getting bored.
ベル坊が退屈しないようにって
押し付けられたんだよ。
チャー！アイ！ア～イ…！！
A stuffed animal? And
this is a picture book...
ぬいぐるみ…
こっちは絵本か。
It might be called the "Demon World", but
children's toys are pretty much the same, huh?
魔界っつっても　子供向けの
おもちゃは変わんね～んだな～。
（アクババ）ウゲケッ！
（古市）ぬわっ！うぐぐ…。
（カエル）グエッ！
（爆発音）
（アクババ）グエ～ッ！！
FYI, that's a pop-up book of magical
beasts and an "Exploding Croaker".
あ～ちなみに今のは
『飛び出せ　絵本怪獣』と→
『爆発ゲロッピ』だな。
火薬の量に自信ありだそうだ。
They seem quite proud of the
amount of gunpowder used.
How can you sound so calm?!
（古市）なに　しれっと言ってんだ！
Well, just thought I'd let you get a
taste of the crap I've been through.
いや～　オレがした苦労を
味わってもらいたくてな～。
（古市）クッ…男鹿　てめ～！
Oga, you bastard!
And this is the "Fun Playtime
Explosion Orchestra",
で！こっちが
『わいわい爆発オーケストラ』→
and this is the "Fully Automatic
Assassination Doll".
で　こっちが『全自動暗殺人形』。
Yeah. I think just the names
disqualify these as toys...
（古市）いや　名前の時点で
おもちゃとして失格だろ。
No kidding.
だな。みょ～なことになる前に
突っ返した方が…。
We'd better return them quick
before things get weird.
ダーブ！
（２人）うわ～！！
アイ～　ダーッ！
ダーブ！
♪♪～
What the...
アイ！アイ…！！
What the hell have you done to us?
何やらせんだ！
はい～っ。
They won't come off! What's going on?
外れね～。ど～なってんだ！
（ピロリ～ン）（２人）んっ？
Let's Play Make-Believe!
Demon World Doctor Edition!
（薬箱）ごっこ遊び
魔界のお医者様バージョン。（２人）はぁ！？
Playing pretend doctors and nurses,
let's raise a child full of compassion!
（薬箱）ナースと　お医者さんの
ごっこ遊びで→
感情豊かな
お子様を育てましょう。→
In order to be more realistic,
リアルさを追求したため
そのコスチュームは→
the costumes are permanent unless the one
playing the role of doctor cures a patient!
お医者さん役の方が　ケガ人の
治療しないと一生取れません。
Here we go with the
unwanted features again...
その設定いらね～って…。
Seriously, they ain't comin' off, no
way! Takin' em off ain't cool! (LOL)
（薬箱）マジで取れません。
取れへんかったら→
かっこ悪いな～自分（笑）　アハ！
I said keep the LOLs to yourself!
笑うなっつってんだろ～！
くっそ～！
Damn it!
Seriously? For the rest of our lives?
マジか？これ。一生このままかぁ。
Of course not!
んな訳ね～だろ！
でもよ～→
But... Baby Beel is the doctor...
たぶん　医者役って
ベル坊だよなぁ？→
That guy's never gonna be
able to heal any patient...
こいつにケガ人の治療なんて
できるわけね～だろ。
アイ！ダーダッ！
アイ～！！
（２人）ハァ…。
ど～すんだよ　男鹿。オイ！
What'll we do, Oga?
Hey...
This is a chance.
チャ～ンス！
え？
Listen up, Furuichi.
いいか　古市。
こいつは　周りの奴を→
This thing spreads the more I
beat the crap out of people.
ボコボコにすりゃ～するほど
広がっちまう。
（古市）あ　ああ…。
Right.
Then shouldn't it retract the
more I go and cure people?
なら逆に！周りの奴を治せば
治すほど引っ込むんじゃね～か？
T-That's what you think?
そ　そんなもんなのか？
There's no way I can stay good
for who knows how many days!
あと何日も　おとなしく
してられっか！
I'll take this playtime,
このごっこ遊びのついでに
こいつを一気に戻してやる！
and use it to revert this
thing in one fell swoop!
ダアー！
おい　ベル坊！
Got it, Baby Beel?
Starting now, you're Doctor
Demon Lord! The Super Doctor!
おめえは今から
ドクター魔王だ！
スーパーお医者さんだ！
アイー？
Now get out there and heal people, damn it!
かたっぱしから
治療していくぞ～！
ダーブ！！
ハハハ！
ダア！
ハァ…。
It's not like we even know
how to use this stuff...
だいたい　こんなもん使い方
わかんねぇぞ。→
これ魔界の薬だろ？
It's Demon World medicine.
アホか　古市　んなもん
バカ正直に使う必要ねぇだろ。
You're an idiot, Furuichi. There's no
reason for us to actually use that stuff.
Nurse's Office
This is a school, remember?
ここは学校だぞ。
前から思ってたんだけどよ→
You know, I've been wondering
this for a while now...
ここの教師って普段
なにやってんだ？
What do the teachers in
the school actually do?
くそっ！こうなったら
この薬箱を使うしかね～か。
Shit. I guess we have to use the
medicine in that box after all.
なんに使うんだ？これ。
What're these for?
During the hard days of study for entrance exams,
unwanted magic power and fatigue can easily build up!
日々の受験勉強には　いらない
魔力や疲（つか）れが　たまりがち。
受験あんだ　魔界。
The Demon World has entrance exams?
For times like that, use this:
"Magic Power Sucky-Suck"
（薬箱）そんな時には　これ！
Place it where you want, and amazingly, it
sucks the unwanted magic power right out of you!
気になる所に貼れば
あら不思議。→
余分な魔力と力を
吸い取ってくれます。→
It's not healthy to hold it in!
がまんは体に良くないぞ～。
So it's like, a compress?
ようするにシップか！
I don't really get the magic
power part, but I think so.
魔力ってのが　よくわかんねぇけどたぶん　そうだろ。
って…ああ！
ダア！
アブブブ。
おちつけ！ベル坊！
Calm down, Baby Beel!
アイ？あっ！アアーッ！
お　おい！ベル坊！うお！
Hey...
Baby Beel!
やめろ！ベル坊！おちつけ！
（ドタン！バタン！）
You kiddin' me?
（不良）マジかよ？
（不良）マジマジ。メシ時は穴場
なんだよ。ここのベッド。
No, man. I'm serious. These beds
are the best place to eat lunch.
（爆発音）
（不良達）かはっ！
ヤベ！
よ～し　患者ゲット！
Oh, crap!
Perfect, our first patients!
え？
だあ～！やべえ！
Oh, no!
What have you done?
何がしてえんだ！てめえは！
オレに聞くなよ！
Don't ask me!
Caution! Caution!
（薬箱）注意　注意。→
If you over flow the magic power capacity...
なお　魔力は一定の許容量を
超えると→
...it will explode!
爆発します！→
And it goes without saying that using it on
people with high magic power is strictly prohibited!
言うまでもないけど
魔力が高い人への使用は厳禁。
（ブッブー）
If you self destruct, your
friends will all laugh at you!
（薬箱）自爆したら友達に
笑われちゃうぞ！
Wait, wait, hold it! Down boy!
まてまてまて！こらえろ　男鹿。→
We need to search for something we can use fast!
早く使えそうな物を
さがさねぇと！
グッ。
ダーブッ！
What's this?
なんだ？これ。
It's an anal probe for magical beasts!
Try using it if your pet
has stomach problems!
（薬箱）
ペットが　お腹を壊したら使おう。
がまんは体に良くないぞ。→
It's not healthy to hold it in!
人に向けて使っちゃダメだぞ。
（ブッブー）
Do not use on humans!
ダーブッ！
こ　これは！？
A-And this is?
A baby dragon cooling spray!
If you burn yourself, this
will cool it right down!
（薬箱）
やけどをしたらすぐに冷やそう。
がまんは体に良くないぞ。
It's not healthy to hold it in!
Ooh, I think we could use this!
（古市）おっこれ使えそう！
But if the dragon gets in a bad mood...
（薬箱）ただし　ドラゴンの
機嫌をそこねると→
...it'll go wild, and you'll
be swimming in a sea of fire!
暴れちゃって一面　炎の海だぞ。
Seriously, what's with the extra features?
だから　その設定　いらねぇって。
Then how about this?
（古市）んじゃ！これは？
The Unicorn Syringe!
It'll even pierce through iron!
（薬箱）鉄をも　つらぬく。
（古市）死ぬわ！
That's deadly!
And this?
これは！？
Blackened Char X-Ray Machine!
Blackened Char?
（古市）黒コゲって…。
Ass-mask!
なんで　しりなんだよ！
Why is it an ass?
ハアハア…じゃあ
こりゃなんだ？
Then what about this?
It's an explosive korobokkur!
One blast, and you're charcoal!
（薬箱）一発で辺りは黒コゲだ。→
Use it whenever you have pent up rage!
うっぷんが　たまったら使おう。
がまんは体に良くないぞ。
It's not healthy to hold it in!
ただの武器じゃね～か。
Great. Another weapon.
Damn it!
クソ！
（薬箱）グエッ。
There isn't a single useful thing in here...
ロクなもん　ねえじゃねぇかよ。
（古市）で　どうするんだよ。
So, what'll we do?
こうなったら手あたり次第
しかね～だろ！
In this case, we'll have to wing-it!
Really?
やっぱり？
行くぜ！
Let's do it!
It's healin' time!
治療開始だ！
ダーブッ。
Too bad, you know?
（真田兄）しゃ～ね～な。
（真田弟）それに乗ってやる。→
That's how it's goin' down.
We'll team up just for now.
一時的に手ぇ組んでやるよ。
（阿部）気に入らないがな。
I don't like this at all.
This ain't my style either, you know.
（下川）オレだって不本意だぜ。
だが　これは　またとない
チャンスだ。
But this is a chance that
might not come again.
If we do in Oga right after
he got Kanzaki and Himekawa...
神崎・姫川をやって
調子づいてる男鹿を→
オレ達がやれば…。
一気にオレ達の名も上がるか。
Our names will rise straight to the top!
Sure. With the four of
us at once, even Oga...
な～に　オレ達が４人いっぺんに
かかれば男鹿だって。
Hey, did you hear?
（不良）≪おい！聞いたか！→
男鹿が保健室を
占拠したらしいぞ！≫
Oga's taken over the nurse's office!
（真田兄弟・下川・阿部）へへへ…。
（真田兄弟・下川・阿部）あ～！
Healing burn wounds? More like freezing
people in solid blocks of ice!
何がヤケドを治療するだ！
もれなく氷づけじゃね～か！
Stop it, Oga!
（古市）や　やめろ～！男鹿！
（男鹿・古市）ギャー！
な　なんだ？今の。
あ　あれ凍ってんのか！？
What was that?
A-Are they frozen?
ゴクン。
お　おい　下川！
H-Hey, Shimokawa!
（アクババ）グゲエー　グゲー。
グエエー！
待て　ベル坊。なんか泣いてるぞ。
Wait, Baby Beel... It seems to be crying.
This thing didn't have an
upset stomach to begin with.
そもそも腹こわしてね～だろ。
そいつ。
ダーブ！
（アクババ）グエー！
（下川）アアーッ！
ハァハァハァ…。
G-Good night...
グ…グッナイ。
（真田弟）お　おい。
H-Hey!
ひゃあ！
中　どうなってんだよ。
What happened, man?
A pink and black nurse... Oga, as a nurse...
ピンクと黒のナースで→
男鹿がナースで　怪鳥が泣き叫び赤ちゃん　大喜び。
A monster bird was crying in pain...
And a baby was having a ball...
お　おい　下川？
ギャハハ！
Come on, Shimokawa...
Yes... I'm sure I'm just hallucinating
from lack of sleep...
そうだよ。
ただの寝不足から来る幻覚で…。
（ガラガラガラッ）
ひゃあ！
お　おい…。
（真田兄弟）あ…あ…。
ハッ！
患者さま～。
Welcome, good patient!
いらっしゃ～い！
Shimokawa!
ゲッ！
Go get 'em, Baby Beel!
いけ！ベル坊！
ダーブッ！
（下川）ギャー…！
S-Shimokawa!
（真田兄）し　下川～！
（真田兄弟）ウゲー！
G-Good...
グッグッ…。
ナイッ。
...night.
（真田兄弟）あああ～。ギャー！
Welcome!
いらっしゃ～い。
ああ…。
Furuichi, hold them down!
古市　こっち押さえつけろ！
（古市）何やってんだよ。
What are you doing?
こうなったら手当たり次第だ！
I'm winging it!
Have at 'em, Baby Beel!
いけ！ベル坊！
ダーブッ！
（真田兄弟）ギャー！
あ…ああ…。
Ryuuichi...
（阿部）竜一…竜二…下川。
Ryuuji...
Shimokawa...
ハーハー。
（ピチョン）
ヒイッ！
グハー…よし！
サササッ！ん！
しゃくしゃくしゃく。
おお！
ポーッ。
Keep your "Puwah!"s to yourself!
ポッじゃねえよ！患者さま…
１匹　追加だ！
Looks like we got ourselves another patient!
うわ～！
ああ！真田兄弟！→
The Sanada Brothers!
Shimokawa!
下川！
（アクババ）ホーゲー！
A b-bird...
（阿部）と　とり！？
（アクババ）ホゲー！
（阿部）ノー！あああ～！
Don't worry.
安心しな！全員　治療中だよ。
They're all being treated.
Now... Let's cure you!
さあ～治しましょう。
ダー。
Principal
Don't!
（阿部）やめて～！！
ダッブー　アイー　アウー。
もう試すもんがねえぞ。
That's enough experimentation...
あ～。
ん？自爆すっか！
Let's blow everything up!
アホ！くだらねえ事
いってんじゃねえよ。
Idiot.
Don't be stupid, man.
ハイハイ…ん？
Yeah, yeah...
Hey.
おい！
あ？
ベル坊の付けてる
あれなんだ？
What's that thing Baby Beel has on?
（古市）治療器具じゃね～の？
アイー。
Isn't that some kind of medical device?
（薬箱）
ウロボロスのホーリーライト～。→
It's Uroboros's Holy Light!
Shine the light on a patient, and amazingly,
怪我人にピカッと当てれば
あら不思議。→
あっという間に怪我が治ります。→
their injuries will be cured, just like that!
Relax, feel better! It's
not healthy to hold it in!
これでラクチン。
がまんは体に良くないぞ。
Tell us that in the first place!
最初から　それを言えや！
ムダな時間をくったぜ。
Damn it, we wasted a hell of a lot of time.
ベル坊！
ダーブ。
Baby Beel!
Face front for me, 'kay?
ちょっと前向いてろ。
アイ？
Congratulations!
（薬箱）オメデトウゴザイマス！
ああ！
おお～！
やった～！
つかれたぁ。
All right!
I'm so tired...
We did it!
やったよ～！
アイヤ！
（阿部）男～鹿～。
Oga!
てめえ　よくも～！
How dare you!
Ow!
（薬箱）
イタ！あきまへん　あきまへん。
あきまへん。
うっ！
お！
（カチッ）
（コロボックル）キャハハ。
（爆発音）
Principal
ふ…ふふふ。
I thought I'd finally got it to revert...
ようやく戻ったと
思ったのによ～！
What the hell have you done, you bastard?
何やってくれてんだよ　てめえら！
ええ～！オレらは関係ねえだろ！
But I didn't do nothin'!
グッナイ。
（真田兄）あ～ん？
Good night?
テヤーッハッハ！
（真田兄弟・下川・阿部）ひぃー！
Principal
（ドアの開閉音）
（爆発音）
（真田兄弟・下川・阿部）
グッナーイ！
ん？遅かったな。
You're late.
ふん！
It looks like you've done well in your
role as parent to the Demon Lord.
魔王の親としてのつとめを
しっかり　はたしてきたようだな。
フフフフ…。
See what I can do when I try?
オレが本気を出しゃあ
こんなもんよ～！
ナーッハハハハ！
ダッダー。
Isn't that right, Baby Beel?
な～ベル坊！
ダーブ！
ナーッハハハハ！アーッハハハ！
フッ。
What's the matter, Baby Beel?
It seems that the young Master
wants a friend of a similar age.
Anyway, how old is Baby Beel?
It is rude to ask a Demon Lord his age!
For now, hurry to the park.
Seriously?
Next time on Beelzebub: The Demon
Lord Makes his Debut at the Park.
By the way, how old are you--?